export const questions = [
  { id: 1, question: 'Who is president director of Seiko Epson Corporation?', answer: 'junkichi yoshida' },
  { id: 2, question: 'When was PT Indonesia Epson Industry founded? (write in format MM-yyyy)', answer: '07-1994' },
  { id: 3, question: 'How much employee in IS Promotion?', answer: '63' },
  { id: 4, question: 'How much sub-division of IS Promotion?', answer: '5' },
  { id: 5, question: 'Who is latest president director of PT Indonesia Epson Industry?', answer: 'emile pattiwael' },
  { id: 6, question: 'Who is 3rd president director of PT Indonesia Epson Industry?', answer: 'watanabe kazuyoshi' },
  { id: 7, question: 'When Mr. Zainuri joined in ISP Department? (write in format MM-yyyy)', answer: '04-2025' },
  { id: 8, question: 'When is annual party of 30th anniversary PT Indonesia Epson Industry? (write in format dd-MM-yyyy)', answer: '27-04-2025' },
  { id: 9, question: 'When was PT Indonesia Epson Industry start operate? (write in format MM-yyyy)?', answer: '04-1995' },
  { id: 10, question: 'What is band name of guest star in 30th annniversary PT Indonesia Epson Industry?', answer: 'pagiboeta' }
]
